Hello friends, welcome to the Investment Information
YouTube channel. In
today's video, we will
talk about a total of six companies with Indian Bank
which have announced a dividend
and have set an ex-date for the dividend on
7 June
2024. First of all, let's talk about Home First
Finance Company India Limited.
When I am shooting this video, the
share price of this company is
Rs 8165 and the market capitalization of this company
is more than Rs 7000 crore. The
52 week high of this company is
Rs 1061 and the 52
week low of this company is
Rs 70530. This company has
announced a final dividend of three rupees and 40 paise
and this company has set an ex-date for the dividend on
7 June
2024. Now, let's talk about ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company Limited.
When I am shooting this video, the
share price of this company is
Rs 15790 and  The market capitalization of this company is
around Rs 78 thousand crores
and the 52 week high of this company is
Rs 1747 and the 52 week low of this company is
Rs 116925 and the company has announced a final dividend of Rs 6
and the
ex-date to pay it is
June 7,
2024. Now let's talk about India Mart Intermesh
Limited. When I am shooting this video, the
share price of this company
is
Rs 241970 and the market capitalization of this company
is more than Rs 14 thousand crores
and the 52 week high of this company
is
3335 points of Rs 55 and the 52 week low of this company is
Rs 2393 35 and the company has announced a final dividend of ₹20
and the
ex-date to pay it is
June 7, 2024. Now let's talk about Indian Bank.
When I am shooting this video, the
share price of this company is  The price is
Rs 56890 and the market capitalization of this company
is more than Rs 76 thousand crores
and the 52 week high of this company
is
Rs 59690 and the 52 week low of this company is
Rs 26805 and the company has
announced a final dividend of ₹12 and the
ex-date to pay it is
June 7,
2024. Let's talk about JM Financial
Limited. When I am shooting this video, the
share price of this company
is Rs 78 65 and the
market capitalization of this company is more than Rs 7000 crores
and the 52 week high of this company
is Rs 114 85 and the 52
week low of this company is
Rs 6810 and the company has
announced a final dividend of Rs 2 and the
ex-date to pay it is
June 7, 2024. Let's talk about Uno Minda
Limited. When  When I am shooting this video, the
share price of this company
is Rs 849 and the
market capitalization of this company is more than Rs 48 thousand crores
and the
52 week high of this company is
Rs 928 95 and the 52 week low of this company
is
Rs 5450 and this company has
announced a final dividend of Rs 1.35
and the ex-date for this is
June 7,
2024. So friends, if you liked this video,
then like this video,
subscribe to the channel, then let's meet
tomorrow at 11:00 am. Bye bye, Tata.